

Delft, South-Holland linkedin.com/in/wouterjmeijer portfolio: hOuter.github.io

Summary

Working a business role at a scale-up allowed me to get hands-on experience with marketing, client-facing communications, stakeholder awareness and sales. These skills are complementary to my interdisciplinary engineering competencies as listed below. My academic interests are with the cognitive aspects of robotics.

Education

## Delft University of Technology - MSc. Cognitive Robotics

2019 - Present

Experience with: Machine & Deep Learning, Optimisation, Motion Planning, Machine Perception, Data Analysis & Visualisation, Signal Processing, System Identification, Filtering, Dynamics, Intelligent Vehicles, Man-Machine Interaction, Control, Neuromechanics.

#### Delft University of Technology - BSc. Mechanical Engineering

2014 - 2019

Minor in Electrical & Biomedical Engineering

Bachelor Thesis @ Systems & Control: "Robot Localization based on collisions and IMU"

### Stedelijk Gymnasium Haarlem - VWO NT/NG

2014

## **Experience**

#### **Skelex - Business Development**

September 2018 - 2020, Rotterdam

I represented Skelex at numerous events and advised businesses on adopting exoskeleton technology in their workforce. Additionally I set up and orchestrated a campaign to raise exoskeleton awareness and find new customers in the Shipbuilding Sector. I supervised 3 groups of marketing students to execute this campaign.

### Freelance - Developer

June 2018 - present, Delft

One project involved building a web calculator to calculate the ROI for refitting light sources with LED's in office buildings. This project was commissioned by a large light source manufacturer.

#### **Mechnificent - Treasurer**

March 2016 - Mar 2017, Delft

With a team of 6 Mechanical Engineering students orchestrate the logistics, location, safety and organisation of a party for 1250 students.

# Skills

- English
- French, German, Spanish
- Solidworks/CAD
- Coding

Cambridge Advanced English

Basic

Mechanical Design - Associate level

Python (num.py, tf, plot.ly, pandas, pyTorch,

Keras, scipy, gym)

C++ (ROS, OpenCV, pcl)

Matlab

JavaScript (bootstrap)